Guide to the Facilities Construction and Renovation, School of Medicine, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Facilities Construction and Renovation, School of Medicine, Yale University, records
1992-2008
RU 979
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
139
(139 boxes)
The records consist of project management and construction files of the Facilities Construction and Renovation, Yale School of Medicine.
Yale University. School of Medicine
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 46-A (YRG 46-A), Records and materials broadly documenting Yale buildings, facilities, and grounds.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The records were transferred from Facilities Construction and Renovation, 2005-2008
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the records is restricted. See inventory for details
Arrangement
The records are arranged by accession
Biographical / Historical
The Facilities Development and Operations Department is responsible for space planning, renovation and new construction, daily maintenance and cleaning, and asset management at the Yale School of Medicine
Scope and Contents
The records consist of project management and construction files of the Facilities Construction and Renovation, Yale School of Medicine
College buildings -- Design and construction; College buildings -- Maintenance and repair; Yale University -- Buildings; Yale University. School of Medicine
- YSM Facilities Project files, 1992-1998; Accession 2005-A-196
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2033
  - YSM Security; 950306-11 (Box 5)
  - YSM Tunnel Sec. Gates; non-cap (Box 49)
- Project management records of the Facilities, Development and Operations Dept., circa 1993-2001; Accession 2006-A-092
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2036
  - YSM Ext. Photo Survey; non-cap, 1999 May 25 (Box 9)
- Closed capital projects, 1998-2006; Accession 2007-A-161
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2041
  Scope and Contents
  Arranged by project
  - YSM Environmental Rooms Upgrade; 01103101, 2001-2006 (Box 1, Folder 71 - 78)
  - YSM Humidification Upgrade; 99090901, 1999-2006 (Box 1, Folder 79 - 84)
  - YSM HVAC Upgrades; 01090502, 2001-2006 (Box 1, Folder 85 - 92)
  - YSM Sprinkler Head Replacement; 99091401, 1999-2006 (Box 1, Folder 93 - 98)
  - YSM Steam Trap and Condensate Pipe Mods.; 00091901, 2000-2006 (Box 1, Folder 99 - 104)
  - YSM Systems Support Equipment Upgrades; 01050904, 2001-2006 (Box 1, Folder 105 - 112)
  - YSM BAS Hardware/Software Upgrade Ph 1; 03072202, 2003-2006 (Box 7, Folder 360 - 366)
  - YSM Egress Stair Upgrades; 03012301, 2003-2006 (Box 7, Folder 367)
- Closed capital project records, 2000-2008; Accession 2009-A-158
  Closed until Jan 1, 2044
  - YSM West of Cedar Bldg Separation - Ph2; 04073002, 2000-2008 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - YSM BAS Hardware/Software Upgrades; 04011302, 2000-2008 (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - YSM Cold Room Upgrades Ph 3; 04060903, 2000-2008 (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - YSM Backfill; 02090402, 2000-2008 (Box 6, Folder 88-91)
- Congress Avenue building CHEFA files, 1998-2008; Accession 2009-A-182
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2044
- Sterling Hall of Medicine lab renovation records, 1999-2007; Accession 2009-A-183
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2043
- Capital project records, 2003-2008; Accession 2010-A-038